withluv.com 2013-04-02

# 

### The following contains the privacy policies and terms of withluv.com.

## Information Collection & Use

### Registration

In order to use some parts of this Web site, you must first complete the registration form and create a user name and password.  During registration you are required to give contact information (such as name and email address). We use this information to contact you about the services on our site in which you have expressed interest.   

WithLuv.com is the sole owner of the information collected on www.withluv.com. WithLuv.com collects personally identifiable information from our users at several different points on our Web site.

### Orders

If you purchase a product or service from us, we request certain personally identifiable information from you on our order form. You must provide contact information (such as name, email, and billing address) and financial information (such as credit card number, expiration date). 

We use this information for billing purposes and to fill your orders.  If we have trouble processing an order, we will use this information to contact you.

New members receive a welcome email containing their username and password in addition to instruction on how to use the website.

### Surveys or Contests

From time-to-time we may provide you the opportunity to participate in contests or surveys on our site.  If you participate, we will request certain personally identifiable information from you. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and you therefore have a choice whether or not to disclose this information.  The requested information typically includes contact information (such as name and address), and demographic information (such as zip code). 

We use this information to continually adjust our offering to our customers needs and to monitor perceived levels of customer service

We will not share the personally identifiable information you provide through a contest or survey with other third parties unless we give you prior notice and choice.

### Special Offers and Updates

We will occasionally send you information on products, services, special deals, and promotions. 

Out of respect for your privacy, we present the option not to receive these types of communications.  Please see the Choice and Opt-out. 

### Service-related Announcements

We will send you strictly service-related announcements on rare occasions when it is necessary to do so.  For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance, we might send you an email. 

Generally, you may opt-out of these communications, although they are not promotional in nature.  You may opt-out of these communications.  Please see Choice and Opt-out.

### Customer Service

Based upon the personally identifiable information you provide us, we will send you a welcoming email to verify your username and password.  We will also communicate with you in response to your inquiries, to provide the services you request, and to manage your account. We will communicate with you by email or telephone, in accordance with your wishes.

### Profile 

We store information that we collect through cookies, log files, and clear gifs, to create a profile of your preferences.  We tie your personally identifiable information, and your purchasing history, to information in the profile, in order to provide tailored promotions and marketing offers and to improve the content of the site for you. 

We do not share your profile with other third parties. 

### Supplementation of Information 

We do not supplement the personal information you submitted to us with any information from third party sources. __

## Information Sharing and Disclosure

### Aggregate Information (non-personally identifiable)

We do not share aggregated demographic information about our user base with our partners and advertisers.  

### Personally identifiable information

We do not share Personally Identifiable Information Personally Identifiable Information with Third Parties.

### Legal Disclaimer

We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web site

### Choice/Opt-out

If you no longer wish to receive our newsletter and promotional communications, you may opt-out of receiving them by following the instructions included in each communication or by emailing us at [info@withluv.com](mailto:info@withluv.com). 

### Log Files

As is true of most Web sites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files.  This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data. 

We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. 

We do not link this automatically-collected data to personally identifiable information.  

### Cookies

A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user’s computer for record-keeping purposes. We use session cookies on this site. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site. 

We use only session ID cookies and not persistent cookies.  We use session cookies to make it easier for you to navigate our site. A session ID cookie expires when you close your browser. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. 

This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by WithLuv.com only and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers. 

### Links to Other Sites

This Web site contains links to other sites that are not owned or controlled by WithLuv.com.  Please be aware that we, WithLuv.com, are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. 

We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. 

This privacy statement applies only to information collected by this Web site. 

### Forum/Bulletin Boards/Chat Rooms

If you use a forum, bulletin board or chat room on this site, you should be aware that any personally identifiable information you submit there can be read, collected, or used by other users of these forums, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages.  We are not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit in these forums.

### Access to Personally Identifiable Information

If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may correct, update, delete or deactivate it by making the change on our member information page or by contacting us by telephone at the contact information listed below.

### Security

The security of your personal information is important to us.  When you enter sensitive information (such as credit card number) on our registration or order forms, we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). 

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it.  No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however.  Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can send an email to us at [info@withluv.com](mailto:info@withluv.com) .

### Business Transitions

In the event WithLuv.com goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, your personally identifiable information will likely be among the assets transferred.  You will be notified via email of any such change in ownership or control of your personal information.

### Changes in this Privacy Statement

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. 

We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently.  If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, or by means of a notice on our home page. 

### Contact Us 

If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please email us at [info@withluv.com](mailto:info@withluv.com) .
